<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Notifications Tracker</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="clear_warning">Are you sure you want to delete all the notifications tracker data ?</string>
    <string name="access_serv_warning">Due to a bug in Samsungs\'s Software, you can experience the phone to read aloud some of your actions.\n \n 
        To prevent this, you will need to disable Samsung TTS and Google TTS. This will not affect any app using TTS features.</string>
    <string name="service_warning">Notifications Tracker service is not running currently. This service should be running in order for this app to give correct results.</string>
    <drawable name="focused">#ff5500</drawable>
    <drawable name="selected">#FF00FF</drawable>
    <string name="tut_1_string">Notification spy records all the incoming notifications.\n\nIt can be used to spy on someone or to analyze which app is spamming your mobile with unwanted notifications.</string>
    <string name="tut_2_string">Hide app will hide the app icon but will still record all the notifications in background. Dial the passcode to bring back the app icon. Default code is 0000.\n\nIgnore app will remove the notifications from specific app in this app.\n\nUnwanted apps can be uninstalled by long click on that app.\n\nDelete Icon removes the notification of specific app</string>
    <string name="tut_3_string">Select the ignored apps to remove them from the ignored list.</string>
    <string name="tut_4_string">Turn on the accessibility service in order to allow Notification spy to record all the 3rd party apps.</string>
     
    <string name="refresh">Start Scanning</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_text">Scanning app %1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="app_icon_content_description">Advertising application\'s icon</string>
    <string name="list_item_ad_framework_prefix">Ad framework</string>
    <string name="no_ad_apps">No apps found with notifications add.\n\nIf you\'re seeing notification ads anyway, there\'s probably a new advertising company the detector doesn\'t know about yet.\n\nIf you\'d like to help, you can use the button below to email a list of your installed apps to us (the dnotification tracker developer).\n\n Your email address and installed applications will not be shared with anyone else.</string>
    <string name="report">I\'d like to help!</string>
    <string name="no_report">No, thanks</string>
    <string name="send_email_with">Send the report with:</string>
    <string name="report_email_subject">Notification Tracker Air push Report</string>
	<string name="report_email_body_prefix">I\'d like to help improve the Notification Tracker! Here is a list of potentially suspicious apps I have installed:</string>
	<string name="progress_dialog_title">Scanning&#8230;</string>
	<string name="native_detection_dialog_title">Your device is awesome!</string>
	<string name="native_detection_dialog_message">Good news! You don\'t need this app at all! Just press and hold on the notification for a few seconds, and your device should tell you who is creating it.</string>
	<string name="native_detection_dialog_button_use_native">Thanks, I\'ll do that!</string>
	<string name="native_detection_dialog_button_use_app">It didn\'t work!</string>
	<string name="hide_app">Hiding app will hide the icon but will keep recording all the notification in the background. \n\nDial the passcode from dialer pad to bring back the app icon. \n\nIt takes few seconds to Hide/Unhide the app.</string>
	
	  <style name="ButtonText">
    <item name="android:layout_width">fill_parent</item>
    <item name="android:layout_height">wrap_content</item>
    <item name="android:textColor">#ffffff</item>
    <item name="android:gravity">center</item>
    <item name="android:layout_margin">3dp</item>
    <item name="android:textSize">30dp</item>
    <item name="android:textStyle">bold</item>
    <item name="android:shadowColor">#000000</item>
    <item name="android:shadowDx">1</item>
    <item name="android:shadowDy">1</item>
    <item name="android:shadowRadius">2</item>
    </style>

</resources>


